-=TLF字幕组=-
翻译：诺阿诺阿，驯鹿
翻译：现代孔融让榴莲，茶包泰迪
注释：校对是书刊出版工作中的一道工序
校对：诺阿诺阿
「佩小姐的奇幻城堡」
你是否感到过自己所做的都毫无意义
Do you ever feel like nothing you do matters?
就像在海滩上留下的脚印
You leave footprints on the beach,
第二天便消失不见
and tomorrow they're gone.
就像不断重复的一天又一天
Like it's just today over again.
人们说十几岁时
They say your teen years
就是要交朋友、尽情玩耍
are for making friends and having fun...
对我来说这样更糟
which made me feel even worse.
嗨，艾米，我是杰克
Hey, Amy. It's Jake.
咱俩数学课一起上
I'm in your math class.
嘿，别忘了给自己买成人纸尿裤
Hey, don't forget your adult diapers.
注释：'呵呵' 表无语
Note: indicates frustration.
呵呵
Yeah, right.
杰克，有电话找你
Jake. Phone for you.
但那一天开始，一切都变了
But that day, everything changed.
谢谢你送我，雪莉
Thanks for the ride, Shelley.
怎么让你去照顾你爷爷呢？
So, how come you have to go deal with your grandpa?
我爸他工作忙，走不开
My dad couldn't get out of work.
他还有工作？
I didn't think he worked.
我还是给爷爷打个电话吧
I'm just gonna call Grandpa.
我是亚伯
Hello, this is Abe.
我是杰克
Hey, it's Jake.
别过来！听我说
No! Don't come here. Listen to me.